thomaspink.com 2017-06-10

# Thomas Pink Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

 Thomas Pink is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you – such as when arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks. 

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party (excluding partners from whom you may have linked to our site) without your permission. 

If you have made a purchase from us, we may occasionally update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mail or post. All our customers have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us and/or selected third parties you may opt-out at any time online. 

OPTIMISING USER EXPERIENCE

In order to optimise and enhance the user experience of the Thomas Pink website, we currently use third party User Experience Analytics services such as Crazy Egg (http://www.crazyegg.com) and SessionCam (http://www.sessioncam.com).

Crazy Egg provides us with click tracking, heat mapping and scroll map data which is gathered over a specified and randomly selected period of time. Crazy Egg does not capture any personal information or details.

SessionCam is used to record individual sessions occurring on the website in order to understand user interaction journey and troubleshoot areas where users may have problems using or accessing the website. SessionCam helps us to understand and improve the quality of service offered through the website. SessionCam is recorded infrequently and at random and we do not capture sensitive data like usernames, passwords, credit cards details or other sensitive information. Any data that is transmitted to SessionCam is sent through securely. 

VisualDNA

We use a cookie and a tag of a third-party service provider, VisualDNA, to collect information about users’ browsing activity on our website (not including users’ names, addresses or other personal information). VisualDNA’s cookie and tag allow us and VisualDNA to build profiles so that users’ online experience can be more relevant to their specific interests. You have the right to choose whether or not to accept VisualDNA’s cookie and tag by visiting http://www.visualdna.com/cookie-policy. VisualDNA does not share users’ information with any third party, other than in anonymised, aggregated form. To learn more, visit VisualDNA’s privacy policy at http://www.visualdna.com/privacy-policy.

Notification of Changes

If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it to others.

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.

Scope of this Privacy Statement

This privacy statement applies to our United Kingdom, European, Rest of the World and United States of America web sites.

Security Policy

When you place an order through this web site your personal details are protected from interception assuring your security.

Depending on your browser, you will see a different confirmation that your connection is secure. For the most common browsers, you will see a closed padlock at the foot of the browser.

All transactions are confirmed and authorized by your card issuing bank. Thomas Pink Limited and Thomas Pink Inc. is rigorous in our approach in protecting the cardholder and we may contact you for additional security purposes should we deem this necessary.

Shopping Basket Assistance

When you use our website, details of any products that you seek to purchase and your email address may be collected during your shopping journey. If you do not complete your purchase, we may contact you using these details to offer our assistance or offer you the ability to save the items you had placed into your ‘basket’. This is done to ensure that you were not suffering technical difficulties and to deliver you the best possible online service. This is an optional service. You can choose not to receive our shopping basket assistance emails at any time by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any assistance email. Unsubscribing from our shopping basket assistance emails does not unsubscribe you from any other Thomas Pink newsletters you have voluntarily opted to receive.
